Guide to the Sterling Divinity Quadrangle, Yale University, Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Sterling Divinity Quadrangle, Yale University, photographs
1931-1959
RU 628
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.33
(6 boxes)
The materials consist of photographs documenting the construction of Sterling Divinity Quadrangle at Yale. Also included are interior and exterior views.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged in four series: I. Construction progress photographs, 1931-1957. II. General views, 1931-1959. III. Slides and transparencies. IV. Folio.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs documenting the construction of Sterling Divinity Quadrangle at Yale. Also included are interior and exterior views.
College buildings -- Design and construction; Photographs; Slides (photographs); Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Divinity School
- Construction progress photographs, 1931-1957; Series I
  - 1931 Sept - 1932 Sep, exterior views (Box 1, Folder 1 - 13)
  - Addition, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 14 - 20)
- General views, 1931-1959; Series II
  - Construction aerial views (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Front views (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Oversize, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Formal views, not including Marquand Chapel (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dormitories (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Views from rear, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Marquand Chapel (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Exterior views with people (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Entryways and archways (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Exterior details (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Architecture article, 1933 May (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Drawings (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Interior, Marquand Chapel (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Interior, library (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Interior, general (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Interior, common room (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Interior, dining hall (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Architect's drawings, rejected plan (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Model (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Slides and transparencies, Series III
  - Slides (Box 4)
  - Transparencies
    - Exterior (Box 5)
    - Female dormitory (Box 5)
    - Married quarters (Box 5)
    - Marquand Chapel (Box 5)